A Guide to the Wampler Business Records, 1916-1972: SC 0202
Special Collections, Carrier Library, James Madison University
- Series 2: Correspondence, 1918-1971
  - Correspondence, February 1947 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    B.B. Tucker- State Director of the Production and Marketing Administration for the United States Department of Agriculture.
  - Correspondence, March 1947 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, April 1947 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    Lawrence T. Berry- Assistant Commissioner of the Department of Agriculture and Immigration for the Commonwealth of Virginia.
  - Correspondence, May 1947 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, June 1947 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, July 1947 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    Captain J.E. Schuyler, Governor William M. Tuck.
  - Correspondence, August 1947 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, September 1947 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    H.E. Moskey- Chief of the Veterinary Medical Section for the Food and Drug Administration.
  - Correspondence, October 1947 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Roy W. Lennartson- Associate Director of the Poultry Branch for the United States Department of Agriculture.
  - Correspondence, November 1947 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Raymond V. Long- Executive Secretary of the Advisory Council on the Virginia Economy for the Commonwealth of Virginia.
  - Correspondence, December 1947 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, January 1948 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, February 1948 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Senator Raymond Guest.
  - Correspondence, March 1948 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    Commonwealth of Virginia Department of Agriculture and Immigration, A. Willis Robertson-Senator of Virginia, United World Federalists of Virginia.
  - Correspondence, April 1948 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    Citizens Committee for United Nations Reform.
  - Correspondence, May 1948 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, June 1948 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, July 1948 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    Commonwealth of Virginia Advisory Council on the Virginia Economy.
  - Correspondence, August 1948 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    Commonwealth of Virginia-Virginia State Planning Board.
  - Correspondence, September 1948 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, October 1948 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, November 1948 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, December 1948 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    Board of Trustees Rockingham Memorial Hospital, Rockingham Library Association, United States Senate Committee on Banking and Currency, Minister of Agriculture for the Republic of Cuba.
  - Correspondence, January 1949 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Commonwealth of Virginia State Board of Education, Department of Agriculture, Congressman Burr P. Harrison, H.S. Gutteridge Department of Agriculture.
  - Correspondence, February 1949 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Senator John S. Battle, Commonwealth of Virginia Department of Agriculture and Immigration, Congress of the United States House of Representatives.
  - Correspondence, March 1949 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Congressman Burr P. Harrison, Department of Agriculture, H.S. Gutteridge Department of Agriculture, United States Department of Agriculture Agricultural Research Administration.
  - Correspondence, April 1949 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, May 1949 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Commonwealth of Virginia Department of Agriculture and Immigration, United States Senate Committee on Finance, Senator Harry F. Byrd.
  - Correspondence, June 1949 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Congress of the United States House of Representatives, Senator Harry F. Byrd, Congressman Burr P. Harrison, Senator A. Willis Robertson.
  - Correspondence, July 1949 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    Commonwealth of Virginia State Board of Education, Commonwealth of Virginia Department of Agriculture and Immigration.
  - Correspondence, August 1949 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, September 1949 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Senator Harry F. Byrd, Lawrence Berry Assistant Commissioner of Agriculture.
  - Correspondence, October 1949 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, November 1949 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, December 1949 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, January 1950 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    Department of Agriculture and Immigration Division of Chemistry, Governor John S. Battle.
  - Correspondence, February 1950 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    L.M. Walker Jr. Commissioner of Agriculture, United States Department of Agriculture Production and Marketing Administration, Virginia State Chamber of Commerce.
  - Correspondence, March 1950 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Senator Raymond A. Guest, Parke C. Brinkley- Commissioner of the Department of Agriculture for the Commonwealth of Virginia.
  - Correspondence, April 1950 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    Commonwealth of Virginia Department of Agriculture, R.M. Loughborough- Executive Secretary for the County of Fairfax.
  - Correspondence, May 1950 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    Parke C. Brinkley- Commissioner of the Department of Agriculture for the Commonwealth of Virginia.
  - Correspondence, June 1950 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    J.W. Graham-Department of Agriculture.
  - Correspondence, July 1950 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, August 1950 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, September 1950 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, October 1950 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, November 1950 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, December 1950 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, January 1951 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    Governor John S. Battle.
  - Correspondence, February 1951 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    Norman S. Elliott- Commonwealth of Virginia State Corporation Commission.
  - Correspondence, March 1951 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, April 1951 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    Jos. Wm. Kinghorne- Assistant Director Poultry Branch-United States Department of Agriculture Production and Marketing Administration.
  - Correspondence, May 1951 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    Congressman Burr P. Harrison, Carolyne Brookes- Virginia State Poultry Federation.
  - Correspondence, June 1951 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    Jos. Wm. Kinghorne- Assistant Director Poultry Branch-United States Department of Agriculture Production and Marketing Administration, Governor John S. Battle.
  - Correspondence, July 1951 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    Congressman Burr P. Harrison
  - Correspondence, August 1951 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    Senator Harry F. Byrd, Congressman Burr P. Harrison.
  - Correspondence, September 1951 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, October 1951 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    Selective Service Board.
  - Correspondence, November 1951 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    Stanley J. Marsden- United States Department of Agriculture; Virginia League for Planned Parenthood, Inc.; autobiographical essay to Fred Lang of The Poultryman.
  - Correspondence, December 1951 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, January 1952 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    S.G. Sutton- Commonwealth of Virginia Division of Markets.
  - Correspondence, February 1952 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    Senator Raymond R. Guest, V.S. Shaffer- Virginia House of Delegates, Senator Curry Carter, Governor John S. Battle, James O. Stickley- Virginia House of Delegates, Landon R. Wyatt- Virginia House of Delegates, E. Blackburn Moore- Virginia House of Delegates, D. French Slaughter- Virginia House of Delegates.
  - Correspondence, March 1952 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    Senator Willis A. Robertson, Congressman Burr P. Harrison.
  - Correspondence, April 1952 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, May 1952 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, June 1952 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    W.D. Termohlen- Director of the Poultry Branch for the Department of Agriculture, Jos. Wm. Kinghorne- Assistant Director Poultry Branch-United States Department of Agriculture Production and Marketing Administration.
  - Correspondence, July 1952 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, August 1952 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    Constitutions and By-Laws from the Virginia State Poultry Federation.
  - Correspondence, September 1952 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    Garland Gary- Commonwealth of Virginia Senate, Congressman Burr P. Harrison.
  - Correspondence, October 1952 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, November 1952 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    Charles F. Brannan- Department of Agriculture.
  - Correspondence, December 1952 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    Department of Agriculture, Senator Harry F. Byrd.
  - Correspondence, January 1953 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, February 1953 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, March 1953 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    W.R. Smith- Department of Highways Landscape Superintendent, Parke C. Brinkley- Commissioner of the Department of Agriculture for the Commonwealth of Virginia.
  - Correspondence, April 1953 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    Governor John S. Battle, Parke C. Brinkley- Commissioner of the Department of Agriculture for the Commonwealth of Virginia.
  - Correspondence, May 1953 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, June 1953 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, July 1953 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, August 1953 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    Thomas B. Stanley- Candidate for Governor, Parke C. Brinkley- Commissioner of the Department of Agriculture for the Commonwealth of Virginia.
  - Correspondence, September 1953 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    Congress of the United States House of Representatives.
  - Correspondence, October 1953 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    Parke C. Brinkley- Commissioner of the Department of Agriculture for the Commonwealth of Virginia, Robert W. Burgess- Director Bureau of Census.
  - Correspondence, November 1953 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, December 1953 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    President Dwight D. Eisenhower, Senator Harry F. Byrd Jr., Parke C. Brinkley- Commissioner of the Department of Agriculture for the Commonwealth of Virginia, Congressman Burr P. Harrison.
  - Correspondence, January 1954 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    W.D. Termohlen- Director of Production and Administration for the Department of Agriculture, Senator Harry F. Byrd, Senator A. Willis Robertson, Congressman William M. Tuck, Congressman Richard H. Poff, Congressman J.T. Broyhill, Congressman William C. Wampler.
  - Correspondence, February 1954 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    Senator A. Willis Robertson, Parke C. Brinkley- Commissioner of the Department of Agriculture for the Commonwealth of Virginia, Lewis L. Strauss- United States Atomic Energy Commission.
  - Correspondence, March 1954 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    Governor Thomas B. Stanley, Parke C. Brinkley- Commissioner of the Department of Agriculture for the Commonwealth of Virginia.
  - Correspondence, April 1954 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    Governor Thomas B. Stanley.
  - Correspondence, May 1954 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, June 1954 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, July 1954 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, August 1954 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, September 1954 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, October 1954 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, November 1954 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, December 1954 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    R. Maclin Smith- Commonwealth of Virginia House of Delegates.
  - Correspondence, January 1955 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, February 1955 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    George W. Dean- State Forester for the Commonwealth of Virginia Department of Conservation and Development.
  - Correspondence, March 1955 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    Garland Gray- Commonwealth of Virginia Senate.
  - Correspondence, April 1955 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    Dan Stickley- President of the Rockingham Development Corporation.
  - Correspondence, May 1955 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, June 1955 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    W.D. Termohlen- The Foreign Service of the United States of America, Parke C. Brinkley- Commissioner of the Department of Agriculture for the Commonwealth of Virginia.
  - Correspondence, July 1955 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    Thos B. Stanley- Commonwealth of Virginia Governor.
  - Correspondence, August 1955 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    Parke C. Brinkley- Commissioner of the Department of Agriculture for the Commonwealth of Virginia, Senator Harry F. Byrd.
  - Correspondence, September 1955 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    Thos B. Stanley- Commonwealth of Virginia Governor, Parke C. Brinkley- Commissioner of the Department of Agriculture for the Commonwealth of Virginia, W.L. Bendix- State Veterinarian for the Commonwealth of Virginia Department of Agriculture and Immigration.
  - Correspondence, October 1955 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    United States Atomic Energy Commission.
  - Correspondence, November 1955 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    Rodney C. Berry- Director for the Virginia Department of Agriculture Division of Chemistry.
  - Correspondence, December 1955 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, January 1956 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    Parke C. Brinkley- Commissioner of the Department of Agriculture for the Commonwealth of Virginia, Virginia Department of Agriculture Division of Chemistry and Foods.
  - Correspondence, February 1956 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    A. Willis Robertson- United States Senate Committee on Appropriations, W.L. Bendix- Commonwealth of Virginia Department of Agriculture Division of Animal and Dairy Industries, Congressman Burr P. Harrison.
  - Correspondence, March 1956 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, April 1956 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, May 1956 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    Rodney C. Berry- Commonwealth of Virginia Department of Agriculture and Immigration Division of Chemistry and Foods.
  - Correspondence, June 1956 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, July 1956 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    Congressman Burr P. Harrison.
  - Correspondence, August 1956 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, September 1956 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    Congressman Burr P. Harrison, Senator Harry F. Byrd, G.M. Carman- Research Officer for the Department of Agriculture. Review of Rockingham County Fair.
  - Correspondence, October 1956 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    Senator Floyd Stevens, Hollis Shomo- Supervisor to the Poultry & Egg Section of the Division of Markets for the Commonwealth of Virginia.
  - Correspondence, November 1956 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, December 1956 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    A. Willis Robertson- United States Senate Committee on Appropriations.
  - Correspondence, January 1957 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, February 1957 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, March 1957 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    Richard D. Chumney- Administrative Assistant for the Department of Agriculture and Immigration to the Commonwealth of Virginia.
  - Correspondence, April 1957 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    Governor Thos B. Stanley, Parke C. Brinkley- Commissioner of the Department of Agriculture for the Commonwealth of Virginia.
  - Correspondence, May 1957 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, June 1957 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    Senator Ted Dalton.
  - Correspondence, July 1957 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, August 1957 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    Lawrence T. Berry- Secretary for the Board of Agriculture and Immigration of the Commonwealth of Virginia.
  - Correspondence, September 1957 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    The Virginia State Dairymen's Association, C.E. Bass- County Supervisor of the Farmers Home Administration for the United States Department of Agriculture.
  - Correspondence, October 1957 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, November 1957 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    W.S. Campbell- Department of Conservation for the Commonwealth of Virginia, Parke C. Brinkley- Commissioner of the Department of Agriculture for the Commonwealth of Virginia.
  - Correspondence, December 1957 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    E.V. Coville- Assistant Director for the Division of Markets of the Commonwealth of Virginia, Rodney C. Berry- Director for the Virginia Department of Agriculture Division of Chemistry, T.R. Elliott- District Forester for the Department of Conservation and Development for the Commonwealth of Virginia.
  - Correspondence, January 1958 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, February 1958 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    Governor Lindsey J. Almond, Senator Harry F. Byrd.
  - Correspondence, March 1958 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    Parke C. Brinkley- Commissioner of the Department of Agriculture for the Commonwealth of Virginia, Don H. Spencer- County Supervisor for the Farmers Home Administration for the United States Department of Agriculture.
  - Correspondence, April 1958 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    Gordon Tucker- Supervisor of the Poultry & Turkey Improvement Plans for the Commonwealth of Virginia.
  - Correspondence, May 1958 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, June 1958 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, July 1958 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, August 1958 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, September 1958 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    Governor J. Lindsay Almond, Jr.
  - Correspondence, October 1958 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    Parke C. Brinkley- Commissioner of the Department of Agriculture for the Commonwealth of Virginia, Congressman Burr P. Harrison, Senator Harry F. Byrd.
  - Correspondence, November 1958 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    W.L. Bendix- State Veterinarian for the Commonwealth of Virginia Department of Agriculture and Immigration.
  - Correspondence, December 1958 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    Raymond D. Schar- Department of Agriculture for the Commonwealth of Virginia, Parke C. Brinkley- Commissioner of the Department of Agriculture for the Commonwealth of Virginia.
  - Correspondence, January 1959 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, February 1959 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    Richard D. Chumney- Secretary for the State Board of Agriculture and Immigration to the Commonwealth of Virginia, J.H. Meek- Division of Markets for the Commonwealth of Virginia.
  - Correspondence, March 1959 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    Senator Harry F. Byrd, Congressman Burr P. Harrison, W.R. Crabill- State Board of Education for the Commonwealth of Virginia, A. Willis Robertson-Senator of Virginia, T.R. Elliott- District Forester for the Department of Conservation and Development for the Commonwealth of Virginia.
  - Correspondence, April 1959 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    T.R. Elliott- District Forester for the Department of Conservation and Development for the Commonwealth of Virginia, Parke C. Brinkley- Commissioner of the Department of Agriculture for the Commonwealth of Virginia, J. Paul Williams- Virginia State Poultry Federation.
  - Correspondence, May 1959 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Parke C. Brinkley- Commissioner of the Department of Agriculture for the Commonwealth of Virginia, J. Paul Williams- Virginia State Poultry Federation, Bill King- Virginia Angus Association.
  - Correspondence, June 1959 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    John H. Ralston- President of the Rockingham Farm Bureau.
  - Correspondence, July 1959 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, August 1959 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Senator George S. Aldhizer.
  - Correspondence, September 1959 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    Virginia Beef Cattle Improvement Association.
  - Correspondence, October 1959 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    Governor J. Lindsey Almond.
  - Correspondence, November 1959 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    Congress of the United States- House of Representatives, H.A. Waters- Acting Chief Officer for the Animal Inspection and Quarantine Division of the United States Department of Agriculture.
  - Correspondence, December 1959 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, January 1960 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, February 1960 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, March 1960 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    Andrew W. Cordier- Executive Assistant to the Secretary-General of the United Nations.
  - Correspondence, April 1960 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    United States Department of Agriculture- Animal Husbandry Research Division.
  - Correspondence, May 1960 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, June 1960 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    J.D. Lawrence- President for the Virginia Highway Users Association.
  - Correspondence, July 1960 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    Senator Charles R. Fenwick.
  - Correspondence, August 1960 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    Gordon Tucker- Supervisor for the Poultry and Turkey Improvement Plans for the Commonwealth of Virginia, Senator Charles R. Fenwick, Homer Quann- Candidate for the President of the United States.
  - Correspondence, September 1960 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    S.M. Long Jr.- Chief Taxpayer Information Section for the U.S. Treasury Department.
  - Correspondence, October 1960 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, November 1960 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, December 1960 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    Delta Airlines, Pan American World Airways.
  - Correspondence, January 1961 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    Senator Charles F. Fenwick.
  - Correspondence, February 1961 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    American Airlines.
  - Correspondence, March 1961 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    Virginia Beef Cattle Association.
  - Correspondence, April 1961 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    The Washington Post, Harrisonburg Daily News-Record, American Airlines.
  - Correspondence, May 1961 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    Washington National Airport, Dr. T.P. Koudelka- Division of Animal and Dairy Industry for the Commonwealth of Virginia, T.R. Elliott- District Forester for the Department of Conservation and Development for the Commonwealth of Virginia. State Planters Bank of Commerce and Trusts.
  - Correspondence, June 1961 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    General Dwight D. Eisenhower.
  - Correspondence, July 1961 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    U.S. Selective Service Board.
  - Correspondence, August 1961 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, September 1961 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, October 1961 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, November 1961 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, December 1961 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, January 1962 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, February 1962 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, March 1962 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, April 1962 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    United States Post Office.
  - Correspondence, May 1962 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    United States Department of Agriculture- Agricultural Stabilization and Conservation Service.
  - Correspondence, June 1962 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    United States Department of Agriculture- Agricultural Research Service.
  - Correspondence, July 1962 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, August 1962 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, September 1962 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, October 1962 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    Shenandoah Life Insurance Company.
  - Correspondence, November 1962 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, December 1962 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, January-February 1963 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, March 1963 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, May 1963 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, June 1963 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, July 1963 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, August-September 1963 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, October-December 1963 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, January 1964 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    Stephen McDonogh- Agricultural Counselor for the Embassy of Ireland.
  - Correspondence, February 1964 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, March 1964 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, April 1964 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    Stanley J. Marsden- Physiology Investigations of the Poultry Research Branch for the U.S. Department of Agriculture.
  - Correspondence, May 1964 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, June 1964 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    Brigadier General R.L. Dulaney.
  - Correspondence, July 1964 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, August 1964 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, September 1964 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    L.H. Averill- General Sales Manager of the Chevrolet Motor Division, Elmer Kaylor- Rockingham Farm Bureau.
  - Correspondence, October 1964 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    Senator A. Willis Robertson; Senator Harry F. Byrd; Congressman John O. Marsh Jr. regarding Wampler's support of the Lyndon Johnson/Hubert Humphrey presidential ticket, includes mentions of Civil Rights.